<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">
  <channel>
    <title>Kids Story of the Day</title>
    <link>.</link>
    <description>One random curated podcast from the great wide web, updated daily.</description>
    
      
      
      
      
      
      
      <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Charged up! The science of batteries]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Batteries are everywhere ? they?re in our phones, our computers, our cars, our toys. But how do they work? To find out, we talk to a scientist who?s making really big batteries to store renewable energy, another who?s working on really small ones to power our phones, and we play in a park with a dog.]]></description>
        <link>https://play.podtrac.com/APM-BrainsOn/chrt.fm/track/3G835/play.publicradio.org/npr/o/podcast/minnesota/podcasts/brains_on/2017/12/brainson_20171219_103_20171219_128.mp3</link>
        <guid>https://play.podtrac.com/APM-BrainsOn/chrt.fm/track/3G835/play.publicradio.org/npr/o/podcast/minnesota/podcasts/brains_on/2017/12/brainson_20171219_103_20171219_128.mp3</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 19:59:47 GMT</pubDate>
        <enclosure url="https://play.podtrac.com/APM-BrainsOn/chrt.fm/track/3G835/play.publicradio.org/npr/o/podcast/minnesota/podcasts/brains_on/2017/12/brainson_20171219_103_20171219_128.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"/>
        <itunes:image href="ctphon.github.io/rss-feed/ksotd.png"/>
      </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[What?s Your Idea To Clean Up The Great Pacific Garbage Patch?]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[In 2019, we answered a question about the Great Pacific Garbage Patch, a huge mass of plastic and other trash swirling around in the Pacific Ocean. Mary James heard that episode and was so inspired, she created a device to help clean up the plastic in the ocean. In this episode of But Why, we learn about her invention, the mermicorn! Download our learning guides: PDF | Google Slide | Transcript Listen back to Why Is There A Big Patch Of Garbage In the Pacific Ocean? Kids: we'd like to know what you think could be done about all the garbage in the ocean. Download our learning guide above to draw a picture or describe an invention you would make to help clean it all up. Mary James sent her picture of the mermicorn to the Little Inventors competition, for Canadian children. See Mary's entry here. Her invention has been chosen from among hundreds of other submissions to be turned into a prototype, a model of what the real thing might look like. There are Little Inventors competitions in the UK as well, and lots of countries and organizations sponsor design challenges for kids. See if you can find one where you live!]]></description>
        <link>https://chrt.fm/track/542BDB/www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/dovetail.prxu.org/_/326/fe9e492e-158a-4087-ba5e-359d3ee46a66/ButWhy_Mermicorn_Ep148.mp3</link>
        <guid>https://chrt.fm/track/542BDB/www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/dovetail.prxu.org/_/326/fe9e492e-158a-4087-ba5e-359d3ee46a66/ButWhy_Mermicorn_Ep148.mp3</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 19:32:09 GMT</pubDate>
        <enclosure url="https://chrt.fm/track/542BDB/www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/dovetail.prxu.org/_/326/fe9e492e-158a-4087-ba5e-359d3ee46a66/ButWhy_Mermicorn_Ep148.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"/>
        <itunes:image href="ctphon.github.io/rss-feed/ksotd.png"/>
      </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Emma asks: What if it snowed in summer?]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Sneakers, why?d it have to be sneakers? Whendiana Joan is back to solve the mystery of Howswell?s lost alien and its sneaker-powered Snowship. Will the people of Howswell accept their newest resident, or will this snow alien lead the town to disaster? Tune in and find out! Join our Patreon for Ad-Free stories, a Shout-Out on the show, bonus audio, a better chance of having your question answered, and more! patreon.com/whatifworld Subscribe to What If World wherever you listen: link.chtbl.com/whatifworld. Share questions via Twitter @whatifworldpod, Facebook @whatifworldpodcast, Instagram @whatifworldpodcast, or email whatifworldpodcast@gmail.com What If World is made by Eric O?Keeffe with help from Karen O'Keeffe. Our theme song is by Craig Martinson and our podcast art is by Jason O?Keefe. Additional songs and sound effects from audioblocks.com.]]></description>
        <link>https://traffic.megaphone.fm/ARML4229970627.mp3?updated=1709313945</link>
        <guid>https://traffic.megaphone.fm/ARML4229970627.mp3?updated=1709313945</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 19:07:22 GMT</pubDate>
        <enclosure url="https://traffic.megaphone.fm/ARML4229970627.mp3?updated=1709313945" type="audio/mpeg"/>
        <itunes:image href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ctphon/rss-feed/main/file-1fud5oT66OH3dKckD4OwqiaF.webp"/>
      </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The hows and whys of hair]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[The hair on our heads is on our minds. We have fun with follicles and learn about how they make hair. Our experts help us decipher what makes hair black or brown, blonde or red, and even why it turns gray. From eye lashes to ear and nose hair, this episode has it all. Why do humans have hair and not fur? Why is there hair on the top of our heads? How does hair grow? How does hair become curly or straight? Plus: A brand new Moment of Um answers the question: &quot;Why does my dad get fuzz in his belly button?&quot; This episode is sponsored by Philo (philo.tv/brains), New Cloud Control Cat Litter by Arm &amp; Hammer, Bona Premium Spray Mop (bona.com/brainson) and Goodnight Stories for Rebel Girls the Podcast (rebelgirls.co/podcast). You can support Brains On at brainson.org/donate]]></description>
        <link>https://play.podtrac.com/APM-BrainsOn/chrt.fm/track/3G835/play.publicradio.org/npr/o/minnesota/podcasts/brains_on/2019/04/16/brainson_20190416_162_128.mp3</link>
        <guid>https://play.podtrac.com/APM-BrainsOn/chrt.fm/track/3G835/play.publicradio.org/npr/o/minnesota/podcasts/brains_on/2019/04/16/brainson_20190416_162_128.mp3</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 19:05:47 GMT</pubDate>
        <enclosure url="https://play.podtrac.com/APM-BrainsOn/chrt.fm/track/3G835/play.publicradio.org/npr/o/minnesota/podcasts/brains_on/2019/04/16/brainson_20190416_162_128.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"/>
        <itunes:image href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ctphon/rss-feed/main/file-1fud5oT66OH3dKckD4OwqiaF.webp"/>
      </item>
    
        <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Layla asks: What if a cat, a weasel, and a dragon teamed up to save the world?]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Cthunkle is back and trying to invade the real world via a carnival at Drew?s house. But can a What If World story even happen on What Is World? Find out for yourself! This episode originally aired July 17, 2017. Join our Patreon for Ad-Free stories, a Shout-Out on the show, bonus audio, a better chance of having your question answered, and more! patreon.com/whatifworld Subscribe to What If World wherever you listen: link.chtbl.com/whatifworld. Share questions via Twitter @whatifworldpod, Facebook @whatifworldpodcast, Instagram @whatifworldpodcast, or email whatifworldpodcast@gmail.com]]></description>
        <link>https://traffic.megaphone.fm/ARML1681040414.mp3?updated=1709314054</link>
        <guid>https://traffic.megaphone.fm/ARML1681040414.mp3?updated=1709314054</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 18:20:52 GMT</pubDate>
        <enclosure url="https://traffic.megaphone.fm/ARML1681040414.mp3?updated=1709314054" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[How do squirrels climb trees?]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Squirrels are everywhere...]]></description>
      <link>https://chrt.fm/track/542BDB/www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/dovetail.prxu.org/_/326/7b0d6fdf-ee50-470a-b621-fc17ba450324/ButWhy_Squirrels_Ep166.mp3</link>
      <guid>https://chrt.fm/track/542BDB/www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/dovetail.prxu.org/_/326/7b0d6fdf-ee50-470a-b621-fc17ba450324/ButWhy_Squirrels_Ep166.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 16:46:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://chrt.fm/track/542BDB/www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/dovetail.prxu.org/_/326/7b0d6fdf-ee50-470a-b621-fc17ba450324/ButWhy_Squirrels_Ep166.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"/>
    </item>

    </channel>
</rss>
