<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss
  version="2.0"
  xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">

  <channel>
    <title>Kids Story of the Day</title>
    <link>.</link>
    <description>One random curated podcast from the great wide web, updated daily.</description>
    <itunes:image href="https://ctphon.github.io/rss-feed/ksotd.png"/>
    <media:thumbnail url="https://ctphon.github.io/rss-feed/ksotd.png"/>

      
      
      
    
      
      
      
      
      
      
      <item>
        <title><![CDATA[[RebelGirls] Jazz Jennings: Swimming Upstream]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Jazz Jennings always knew exactly who she was. Even when people excluded or bullied her, she stood up for transgender children like herself. Today, this brave, determined woman uses her voice to advocate for equality and respect for all. You can find Jazz in the new book Rebel Girls: 100 Inspiring Young Changemakers! We're celebrating all September long with two special Changemakers podcast episodes each week. Preorder Rebel Girls: 100 Inspiring Young Changemakers wherever books are sold to learn about how girls just like you are changing the world. This story was produced by Olivia Ri?hard with sound design and mixing by Mumble Media. It was written by Nicole Haroutunian and edited by Abby Sher. Narration by Anjali Kunapaneni. Thank you to the whole Rebel Girls team, who make this podcast possible. Stay rebel!]]></description>
        <link>https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/pdst.fm/e/prefix.up.audio/s/chrt.fm/track/FGADCC/traffic.megaphone.fm/RGS6012279900.mp3?updated=1671583228</link>
        <guid>https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/pdst.fm/e/prefix.up.audio/s/chrt.fm/track/FGADCC/traffic.megaphone.fm/RGS6012279900.mp3?updated=1671583228</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 09:43:35 GMT</pubDate>
        <enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/pdst.fm/e/prefix.up.audio/s/chrt.fm/track/FGADCC/traffic.megaphone.fm/RGS6012279900.mp3?updated=1671583228" type="audio/mpeg"/>
        <itunes:image href="https://ctphon.github.io/rss-feed/ksotd.png"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="https://ctphon.github.io/rss-feed/ksotd.png"/>
      </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[[BrainsOn] How does a match make fire?]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Have you ever seen someone strike a match? The match rubs against a scratchy strip and a split second later ? poof! It makes fire! But how does a match work, anyway?Join Molly and co-host Maxwell as they get all fired up about matches! They?ll explore the three things a fire needs to ignite and learn how lighting a match is just a super fast chemical reaction that sometimes smells like farts. Plus, we?ll hear your hot new names for matches and of course, a new mystery sound!Do you have your Smarty Pass yet?? Get yours today for just $4/month (or $36/year) and get bonus episodes every month, and ad-free versions of every episode of Brains On, Smash Boom Best, Moment of Um, and Forever Ago. Visit www.smartypass.org to get your Smarty Pass today!____________This episode was sponsored by:Sitka Seafood Market - Use promo code Molly35 to receive $35 off your first order. Indeed - Use promo code brainson to receive a $75 sponsored job credit]]></description>
        <link>https://play.podtrac.com/APM-BrainsOn/chrt.fm/track/3G835/play.publicradio.org/npr/o/minnesota/podcasts/brains_on/2024/02/27/brainson_20240227_289_128.mp3</link>
        <guid>https://play.podtrac.com/APM-BrainsOn/chrt.fm/track/3G835/play.publicradio.org/npr/o/minnesota/podcasts/brains_on/2024/02/27/brainson_20240227_289_128.mp3</guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:43:36 GMT</pubDate>
        <enclosure url="https://play.podtrac.com/APM-BrainsOn/chrt.fm/track/3G835/play.publicradio.org/npr/o/minnesota/podcasts/brains_on/2024/02/27/brainson_20240227_289_128.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"/>
        <itunes:image href="https://ctphon.github.io/rss-feed/ksotd.png"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="https://ctphon.github.io/rss-feed/ksotd.png"/>
      </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[[StoriesPod] Syd?s Snow Day]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Today's episode is about a kid named Syd. With an impending math quiz Syd is hoping for a snow day, and luckily their wish comes true! Follow along to find out what Syd gets up to on their day off.
 Draw us a picture of what you? think any of the characters in this story look like, and then tag us in? it on instagram @storiespodcast! We'd love to see your artwork and share? it on our feed!!
 If you would like to support Stories Podcast, you can subscribe and give us a five star review on iTunes, check out our merch at? storiespodcast.com/shop, follow us on Instagram @storiespodcast, or just tell your friends about us!
 Check out our new YouTube channel at youtube.com/storiespodcast. If you've ever wanted to read along with our stories, now you can! These read-along versions of our stories are great for early readers trying to improve their skills or even adults learning English for the first time. Check it out.]]></description>
        <link>https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/traffic.megaphone.fm/STM5806663318.mp3</link>
        <guid>https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/traffic.megaphone.fm/STM5806663318.mp3</guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:43:38 GMT</pubDate>
        <enclosure url="https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/traffic.megaphone.fm/STM5806663318.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"/>
        <itunes:image href="https://ctphon.github.io/rss-feed/ksotd.png"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="https://ctphon.github.io/rss-feed/ksotd.png"/>
      </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[[KidsScienceWeekly] ANCIENT EGYPT: Understanding How Hieroglyphics Really Worked????????]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Get ready for another BIG and BRILLIANT journey through time, space, and the human mind on this week's Science Weekly! We're heading back to Ancient Egypt to unlock the secrets of hieroglyphics, a mysterious language that was lost for thousands of years. Then we zoom inside your head to explore the incredible science of the brain and how this squishy, sparky organ really works. In Science in the News, robotic dogs could soon be helping to fight wildfires, scientists in India have discovered a galaxy that's an incredible 12 billion years old, and Dr Matilda Brindle joins Dan to investigate the science behind the very first human kiss, believed to date back millions of years. We also answer your questions... Charlie wants to know how race cars go so fast, and Mercedes Durham from Cardiff University explains why the Ancient Egyptians wrote in hieroglyphics. Dangerous Dan returns with a tiny dinosaur with a big reputation, the Compsognathus. And in Battle of the Sciences, Daniel Glaser makes the case for neurology, revealing the electrifying science that powers your brain. Plus, we head back to Deep Space High for Space For All, discovering what kinds of space careers are perfect for people who love languages. This week, we learn about: How hieroglyphics worked in Ancient Egypt How the human brain sends messages Robotic dogs and fighting wildfires A galaxy older than most of the universe The surprising history of the first kiss How race cars reach extreme speeds All that and more on this week's Science Weekly!Join Fun Kids Podcasts+: https://funkidslive.com/plusSee omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.]]></description>
        <link>https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/traffic.omny.fm/d/clips/289ceca7-bef3-48af-9f74-a4ba0095cab1/14b69fe4-635d-4253-bccf-aa710001b221/8f46d485-4f63-4368-9f7b-b3b500d6c75a/audio.mp3</link>
        <guid>https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/traffic.omny.fm/d/clips/289ceca7-bef3-48af-9f74-a4ba0095cab1/14b69fe4-635d-4253-bccf-aa710001b221/8f46d485-4f63-4368-9f7b-b3b500d6c75a/audio.mp3</guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:43:38 GMT</pubDate>
        <enclosure url="https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/traffic.omny.fm/d/clips/289ceca7-bef3-48af-9f74-a4ba0095cab1/14b69fe4-635d-4253-bccf-aa710001b221/8f46d485-4f63-4368-9f7b-b3b500d6c75a/audio.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"/>
        <itunes:image href="https://ctphon.github.io/rss-feed/ksotd.png"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="https://ctphon.github.io/rss-feed/ksotd.png"/>
      </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[[WowInTheWorld] Two Whats?! And A Wow! - Out Of This World (encore)]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Why are Mindy and Guy Raz throwing the Solar System a tea party? And why won't Mercury sit still!? Find out what in the world this has to do with the science of the solar system in today's sonic round of Two Whats?! And A Wow! We've got questions AND answers, and it's up to you to find the fact from the fiction about the Solar System!
 
 See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.]]></description>
        <link>https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/pdst.fm/e/rss.art19.com/episodes/2f8bd30d-4a4e-4616-b0ef-1d55e91124e6.mp3?rss_browser=BAhJIgxGaXJlZm94BjoGRVQ%3D--e1fe8381133ee436d645c9120f2b13f7c307fd4d</link>
        <guid>https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/pdst.fm/e/rss.art19.com/episodes/2f8bd30d-4a4e-4616-b0ef-1d55e91124e6.mp3?rss_browser=BAhJIgxGaXJlZm94BjoGRVQ%3D--e1fe8381133ee436d645c9120f2b13f7c307fd4d</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:43:36 GMT</pubDate>
        <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/pdst.fm/e/rss.art19.com/episodes/2f8bd30d-4a4e-4616-b0ef-1d55e91124e6.mp3?rss_browser=BAhJIgxGaXJlZm94BjoGRVQ%3D--e1fe8381133ee436d645c9120f2b13f7c307fd4d" type="audio/mpeg"/>
        <itunes:image href="https://ctphon.github.io/rss-feed/ksotd.png"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="https://ctphon.github.io/rss-feed/ksotd.png"/>
      </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[[But Why] Why Are Cactuses Spiky?]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[What makes a cactus a cactus? And what are you supposed to call a group of these plants--cacti, cactuses, or cactus?! We'll find out in today's episode, as we learn more about the cactus family with Kimberlie McCue of the Desert Botanical Garden in Phoenix, Arizona. She'll answer kid questions about why cactuses are spiky and how they got those spikes, as well as why teddy bear cactuses aren't actually cuddly! Download our learning Guides: PDF | Google Slide | Transcript Those prickly spines that are so characteristic of the cactus family are actually modified leaves! Cactuses don't have the kind of leaves like a maple or oak tree. But they might have had leaves that were at least a little more like that way way back in the past. Over time, those leaves evolved into the spiky spines we see on cactuses today because they help the plants survive in hot, dry environments. Why are cactuses spiky? -Noah, Iowa "They can be a defense mechanism to discourage herbivores - animals that eat plants - from eating the cactus. But, also, spines create shade!" explains Kimberlie McCue. "When you're covered in spines, as the sun moves across the sky, those spines are casting shadows on the body of the cactus. They're little shade umbrellas!" All cactuses are native to desert environments, and some live in places where it never rains at all. So how do they get water to survive? Well, Kimberlie tells us that these plants grow not too far from the ocean. "Early in the morning, there will be fog that comes off the water. Those spines provide a place for the water to condense, form little droplets of water that run down the spine, to the body of the plant, down to the ground and to the roots." Cactuses are also extremely important parts of their desert environments, as they hold soil in place and provide shelter for birds and other animals. Those insects and birds in turn help pollinate the cactus flowers. Cactuses are also an important local food source for humans. Unfortunately, cactuses are in danger from people who poach (illegally take) wild plants from their environment. Kimberlie McCue says one way to help make sure cacti stay healthy and plentiful is to be careful when you buy cactus plants. Check to see where the plant seller got the cactus and make sure they're taking care to be ethical stewards of these plants before you buy.]]></description>
        <link>https://chrt.fm/track/542BDB/www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/dovetail.prxu.org/_/326/6e17899c-dcf1-4e03-9ca6-3331330d4605/ButWhy_Cactus_Ep145.mp3</link>
        <guid>https://chrt.fm/track/542BDB/www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/dovetail.prxu.org/_/326/6e17899c-dcf1-4e03-9ca6-3331330d4605/ButWhy_Cactus_Ep145.mp3</guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 09:43:35 GMT</pubDate>
        <enclosure url="https://chrt.fm/track/542BDB/www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/dovetail.prxu.org/_/326/6e17899c-dcf1-4e03-9ca6-3331330d4605/ButWhy_Cactus_Ep145.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"/>
        <itunes:image href="https://ctphon.github.io/rss-feed/ksotd.png"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="https://ctphon.github.io/rss-feed/ksotd.png"/>
      </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[[StoriesPod] Throwback: The Love Potion]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Today we're doing a throwback episode to one of our favorites from the early days of Stories Podcast. The Love Potion! In this story, based on a traditional Ethiopian fable, a very nervous young man named Abel seeks a magical solution to his struggles, but he needs to retrieve a very special ingredient first! Will he be able to do it? Listen in and find out! And parents, see if you recognize the fun oldie that inspired this episode's song!
 
 
 
 Check out Stories RPG our new show where we play games like Starsworn with all your Max Goodname friends, and Gigacity Guardians featuring the brilliant firefly! https://link.chtbl.com/gigacity
 
 
 
 Draw us a picture of what you think any of the characters in this story look like, and then tag us in it on instagram @storiespodcast! We'd love to see your artwork and share it on our feed!!
 
 
 
 If you would like to support Stories Podcast, you can subscribe and give us a five star review on iTunes, check out our merch at storiespodcast.com/shop, follow us on Instagram @storiespodcast, or just tell your friends about us!
 
 
 
 Check out our new YouTube channel at youtube.com/storiespodcast. If you've ever wanted to read along with our stories, now you can! These read-along versions of our stories are great for early readers trying to improve their skills or even adults learning English for the first time. Check it out.]]></description>
        <link>https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/traffic.megaphone.fm/STM7699623980.mp3</link>
        <guid>https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/traffic.megaphone.fm/STM7699623980.mp3</guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 15:41:43 GMT</pubDate>
        <enclosure url="https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/traffic.megaphone.fm/STM7699623980.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"/>
        <itunes:image href="https://ctphon.github.io/rss-feed/ksotd.png"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="https://ctphon.github.io/rss-feed/ksotd.png"/>
      </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[[But Why] What If You?re Scared To Start School?]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Five-year-old Odin in Wyoming is about to start school and he sent us this question: If I?m terrified about kindergarten do I have to go? What should I do if I?m scared? What if kids are mean to me? In this episode, tips and suggestions from our listeners for kids returning to school, along with answers from guidance counselor Tosha Todd and National Teacher of the Year Juliana Urtubey. Download our learning guides: PDF | Google Slide | Transcript Related Episodes: Why Do We Have To Go To School? First day of school book recommendations from Tosha Todd First Day Jitters Night Before Kindergarten Miss Bindergarten Gets Ready for Kindergarten The Kissing Hand Back to school tips Make a hug button! Draw a heart on the inside of your hand. Draw a heart on your parent?s hand. Squeeze them together to charge your hug button. If you feel nervous at school, push the hug button and it will send you a hug. - Tosha Todd, school guidance counselor Keep a picture of your family in your backpack. You can share with your teacher the things your family does for fun. That will help your teacher understand your family. - Juliana Urtubey, National Teacher of the Year If you're nervous try to have fun and try to make some friends and the school year will be a lot better.- Zoe, 10 Colorado Remind yourself that you are brave and confident. - Clarissa, 8, Ontario Get into a school routine now. Pick out your clothes the night before. Maybe pack your lunch too. - Tosha Todd When I start school I feel nervous, but when I step in I feel ok. For the first few days I play by myself. When those first few days are done, I play with others. - Julius, 8, Ontario Take a deep breath, be kind to someone and they'll be kind to you. - Zoe, 6, California Get everyone's names and if you forget them it's ok to ask again. - Lucy, Vermont Say hi to all the kids. - Ben, 6, Michigan You're going to make friends, and your mom and dad will pick you up; they're not going to leave you there forever. - Sly, 7, New York]]></description>
        <link>https://chrt.fm/track/542BDB/www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/dovetail.prxu.org/_/326/bec8fc84-473d-41d0-8f52-9889c4e189b4/ButWhy_BackToSchool_Ep160.mp3</link>
        <guid>https://chrt.fm/track/542BDB/www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/dovetail.prxu.org/_/326/bec8fc84-473d-41d0-8f52-9889c4e189b4/ButWhy_BackToSchool_Ep160.mp3</guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 01:03:40 GMT</pubDate>
        <enclosure url="https://chrt.fm/track/542BDB/www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/dovetail.prxu.org/_/326/bec8fc84-473d-41d0-8f52-9889c4e189b4/ButWhy_BackToSchool_Ep160.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"/>
        <itunes:image href="https://ctphon.github.io/rss-feed/ksotd.png"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="https://ctphon.github.io/rss-feed/ksotd.png"/>
      </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[[StoriesPod] The Wind in the Willows: The River Bank]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Today's story is adapted from Kenneth Grahame. Join us as a mole goes outside of his comfort zone and has a wonderful adventure on a boat ride with a water rat. 
 Check out Stories RPG our new show where we play games like Starsworn with all your Max Goodname friends, and Gigacity Guardians featuring the brilliant firefly! https://link.chtbl.com/gigacity
 Draw us a picture of what you? think any of the characters in this story look like, and then tag us in? it on instagram @storiespodcast! We'd love to see your artwork and share? it on our feed!!
 If you would like to support Stories Podcast, you can subscribe and give us a five star review on iTunes, check out our merch at? storiespodcast.com/shop, follow us on Instagram @storiespodcast, or just tell your friends about us!
 Check out our new YouTube channel at youtube.com/storiespodcast. If you've ever wanted to read along with our stories, now you can! These read-along versions of our stories are great for early readers trying to improve their skills or even adults learning English for the first time. Check it out.]]></description>
        <link>https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/traffic.megaphone.fm/STM7514636810.mp3</link>
        <guid>https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/traffic.megaphone.fm/STM7514636810.mp3</guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 00:59:13 GMT</pubDate>
        <enclosure url="https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/traffic.megaphone.fm/STM7514636810.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"/>
        <itunes:image href="https://ctphon.github.io/rss-feed/ksotd.png"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="https://ctphon.github.io/rss-feed/ksotd.png"/>
      </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[[GirlTales] Princess Cordelia of Freshwater]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Princess Cordelia leaves the School of Children of Lost Parents to meet the woman who has adopted her. The woman is very serious and only likes things that are absolutely necessary. Plus, the town they will live in has no other people and places to go to! Can Princess Cordelia use her bright imagination to bring this town to life?
 Inspired by Anne of Green Gables by Lucy Maud Montgomery
 Written, Produced, & Performed by Rebecca Cunningham
 Hosts: Arlo & Rebecca
 Original Theme Music: Eli Denby Wood & Amy Gijsbers van Wijk
 For the Grownups!
 Patreon: https://patreon.com/girltales
 Holiday Tales: https://girltalespodcast.com/holidaytales/
 Girl Tales Store: https://girltalespodcast.com/store-2/
 Rebecca?s Newsletter: https://girltalespodcast.us16.list-manage.com/subscribe?u=164c30f0c37a086fa0e32bb5b&id=bdacaecddd
 Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/girltalespodast/
 Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/girltales/
 Girl Tales Grown-Ups Group: https://www.facebook.com/groups/2394948737386136
  See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.]]></description>
        <link>https://chrt.fm/track/53D82/chrt.fm/track/2C52E6/traffic.megaphone.fm/CST3680066516.mp3?updated=1656605019</link>
        <guid>https://chrt.fm/track/53D82/chrt.fm/track/2C52E6/traffic.megaphone.fm/CST3680066516.mp3?updated=1656605019</guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 00:31:53 GMT</pubDate>
        <enclosure url="https://chrt.fm/track/53D82/chrt.fm/track/2C52E6/traffic.megaphone.fm/CST3680066516.mp3?updated=1656605019" type="audio/mpeg"/>
        <itunes:image href="https://ctphon.github.io/rss-feed/ksotd.png"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="https://ctphon.github.io/rss-feed/ksotd.png"/>
      </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[[WowInTheWorld] Need to Settle A Dispute? Try Venom! (Encore - 9/13/21)]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>A new toy craze has taken over the neighborhood, with friends turning into foes over rare ?Boo Boo Beanie Boppers.? Mindy is reminded of a new study that explores the interesting dispute settling tactic of slow lorises. Join Mindy and Guy Raz as they head to the wild forests of Indonesia in search of the world?s most adorable and venomous primates! Can they use what they discover to stop their friends from tearing each other apart over Boo Boo Beanie Boppers? It?s the Who, What, When, Where, Why, How, and Wow in the world of the SLOW LORIS! (Originally aired 11/9/20)</p><p>See Privacy Policy at <a href="https://art19.com/privacy" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">https://art19.com/privacy</a> and California Privacy Notice at <a href="https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info</a>.</p>]]></description>
        <link>https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/pdst.fm/e/rss.art19.com/episodes/cc12b945-7fac-414c-be56-b72175777eac.mp3?rss_browser=BAhJIgxGaXJlZm94BjoGRVQ%3D--e1fe8381133ee436d645c9120f2b13f7c307fd4d</link>
        <guid>https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/pdst.fm/e/rss.art19.com/episodes/cc12b945-7fac-414c-be56-b72175777eac.mp3?rss_browser=BAhJIgxGaXJlZm94BjoGRVQ%3D--e1fe8381133ee436d645c9120f2b13f7c307fd4d</guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 00:26:15 GMT</pubDate>
        <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/pdst.fm/e/rss.art19.com/episodes/cc12b945-7fac-414c-be56-b72175777eac.mp3?rss_browser=BAhJIgxGaXJlZm94BjoGRVQ%3D--e1fe8381133ee436d645c9120f2b13f7c307fd4d" type="audio/mpeg"/>
        <itunes:image href="https://ctphon.github.io/rss-feed/ksotd.png"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="https://ctphon.github.io/rss-feed/ksotd.png"/>
      </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[[WowInTheWorld] Two Whats?! And A Wow! - Hair We Go! (encore)]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Why is Mindy playing basketball with a ball covered in hair? And what does that have to do with the science of HAIR? We've got questions AND answers on today's hair-raising round of Two Whats?! And A Wow! We're challenging you to find facts from fiction about hair!
 
 See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.]]></description>
        <link>https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/pdst.fm/e/rss.art19.com/episodes/25401597-3531-4198-8f3c-4c3cf426bbf1.mp3?rss_browser=BAhJIgxGaXJlZm94BjoGRVQ%3D--e1fe8381133ee436d645c9120f2b13f7c307fd4d</link>
        <guid>https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/pdst.fm/e/rss.art19.com/episodes/25401597-3531-4198-8f3c-4c3cf426bbf1.mp3?rss_browser=BAhJIgxGaXJlZm94BjoGRVQ%3D--e1fe8381133ee436d645c9120f2b13f7c307fd4d</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 23:30:48 GMT</pubDate>
        <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/pdst.fm/e/rss.art19.com/episodes/25401597-3531-4198-8f3c-4c3cf426bbf1.mp3?rss_browser=BAhJIgxGaXJlZm94BjoGRVQ%3D--e1fe8381133ee436d645c9120f2b13f7c307fd4d" type="audio/mpeg"/>
        <itunes:image href="https://ctphon.github.io/rss-feed/ksotd.png"/>
      </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[[WowInTheWorld] Turkey Love (1/30/23)]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Love is in the air for one of our favorite flightless birds... the turkey! Tune in as Mindy and Guy Raz watch a brand new episode of "Fowling In Love," a reality TV show about turkey's mating habits! Find what researchers have discovered about the (tur)key to a good turkey match. It's the who, what, when, where, how and WOW of Turkey Love!</p><p>See Privacy Policy at <a href="https://art19.com/privacy" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">https://art19.com/privacy</a> and California Privacy Notice at <a href="https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info</a>.</p>]]></description>
        <link>https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/pdst.fm/e/rss.art19.com/episodes/725b1c5c-4c5f-429b-8b0e-8fd0e90d9620.mp3?rss_browser=BAhJIgxGaXJlZm94BjoGRVQ%3D--e1fe8381133ee436d645c9120f2b13f7c307fd4d</link>
        <guid>https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/pdst.fm/e/rss.art19.com/episodes/725b1c5c-4c5f-429b-8b0e-8fd0e90d9620.mp3?rss_browser=BAhJIgxGaXJlZm94BjoGRVQ%3D--e1fe8381133ee436d645c9120f2b13f7c307fd4d</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 23:05:23 GMT</pubDate>
        <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/pdst.fm/e/rss.art19.com/episodes/725b1c5c-4c5f-429b-8b0e-8fd0e90d9620.mp3?rss_browser=BAhJIgxGaXJlZm94BjoGRVQ%3D--e1fe8381133ee436d645c9120f2b13f7c307fd4d" type="audio/mpeg"/>
        <itunes:image href="https://ctphon.github.io/rss-feed/ksotd.png"/>
      </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[[StoriesPod] Wylderwood Book 2 (rebroadcast)]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[         <p>Today week we're doing a review of the Wylderwood series before a brand new episode comes out on Friday.</p><p>Check out Stories RPG our new show where we play games like Starsworn with all your Max Goodname friends, and Gigacity Guardians featuring the brilliant firefly! <a href=https://link.chtbl.com/gigacity" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">https://link.chtbl.com/gigacity</a></p><p>Draw us a picture of what you&nbsp;think any of the characters in this story look like, and then tag us in&nbsp;it on instagram @storiespodcast! We'd love to see your artwork and share&nbsp;it on our feed!!</p><p>If you would like to support Stories Podcast, you can subscribe and give us a five star review on iTunes, check out our merch at<a href="http://storiespodcast.com/shop" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;storiespodcast.com/shop</a>, follow us on Instagram @storiespodcast, or just tell your friends about us!</p><p>Check out our new YouTube channel at <a href="http://youtube.com/storiespodcast" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">youtube.com/storiespodcast</a>. If you've ever wanted to read along with our stories, now you can! These read-along versions of our stories are great for early readers trying to improve their skills or even adults learning English for the first time. Check it out.</p><p>See Privacy Policy at <a href="https://art19.com/privacy" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">https://art19.com/privacy</a> and California Privacy Notice at <a href="https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info</a>.</p>       "]]></description>
        <link>https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/rss.art19.com/episodes/4ee84285-d86a-41e3-96f6-fe05894823ca.mp3?rss_browser=BAhJIgxGaXJlZm94BjoGRVQ%3D--e1fe8381133ee436d645c9120f2b13f7c307fd4d</link>
        <guid>https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/rss.art19.com/episodes/4ee84285-d86a-41e3-96f6-fe05894823ca.mp3?rss_browser=BAhJIgxGaXJlZm94BjoGRVQ%3D--e1fe8381133ee436d645c9120f2b13f7c307fd4d</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 09:43:36 GMT</pubDate>
        <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/rss.art19.com/episodes/4ee84285-d86a-41e3-96f6-fe05894823ca.mp3?rss_browser=BAhJIgxGaXJlZm94BjoGRVQ%3D--e1fe8381133ee436d645c9120f2b13f7c307fd4d" type="audio/mpeg"/>
        <itunes:image href="https://ctphon.github.io/rss-feed/ksotd.png"/>
      </item>

    </channel>
</rss>
